export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "Which club has won the most Champions League titles?",
        optionA: "AC Milan",
        optionB: "Real Madrid",
        optionC: "LiverPool",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who is the only player to win the Champions League with three different clubs?",
        optionA: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        optionB: "Ibrahimovic",
        optionC: "Clarence Seedorf",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Three people have won the Champions League a record three times as manager. Who are they?",
        optionA: "Bob Paisley, Carlo Ancelotti and Zinedine Zidane",
        optionB: "Carlo Ancelotti, Mourinho and Zinedine Zidan",
        optionC: "Zinedine Zidan, Carlo Ancelotti and Alex Ferguson",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt: "In which season was the European Cup rebranded as the Champions League?",
        optionA: "1991-92",
        optionB: "1993-94",
        optionC: "1992-93",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which team was the first from the UK to win the European Cup?",
        optionA: "Manchester United",
        optionB: "Celtic (1966-67)",
        optionC: "LiverPool",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt: "The Champions League has been won only once by a team from Romania. Can you name them?",
        optionA: "FC Dinamo Bucuresti",
        optionB: "FC Rapid Bucuresti",
        optionC: "Steaua Bucharest",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who won the UEFA Champions League final in 2004?",
        optionA: "Real Madrid",
        optionB: "FC Porto",
        optionC: "AC Milan",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who is the Champions League's top goalscorer of all time?",
        optionA: "Leo Messi",
        optionB: "Raul Gonzales",
        optionC: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which player holds the record for most Champions League winners' medals?",
        optionA: "Francisco Gento",
        optionB: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        optionC: "Alen Sherar",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which outfield player appeared in the Champions League final in three different decades?",
        optionA: "Buffon",
        optionB: "Rayan Giggs",
        optionC: "Ricardo Kaka",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many goals did Raul score during his champions league career",
        optionA: "71",
        optionB: "75",
        optionC: "81",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many times has a Club won the UEFA European Cup or Champions League on its Home Nationâ€™s soil?",
        optionA: "6 times",
        optionB: "0 times",
        optionC: "2 times",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
]